webwash.net 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy | WebWash

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site,  
subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be  
asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone  
number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site  
anonymously.  
Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance  
your  
experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our  
website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for  
information about cookies and how we use them.  
 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the  
following ways:  
To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the  
information and feedback we receive from you)  
To improve customer  
service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer  
service requests and support needs)  
To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold,  
exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason  
whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of  
delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
To administer a  
contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
To send periodic  
emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used  
to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.  
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails  
that may include company news, updates, related product or service  
information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving  
future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the  
bottom of each email.  
 **How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety  
of  
your personal information when you place an order or access your  
personal information.  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied  
sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer  
(SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers  
database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access  
rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information  
confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social  
security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.  
 **Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider  
transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you  
allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize  
your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your  
shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits,  
and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site  
traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site  
experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party  
service providers to assist us in better understanding our site  
visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the  
information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and  
improve our business.  
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each  
time  
a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via  
your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies  
off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can  
still place orders by contacting customer service.  
 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your  
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted  
third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our  
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this  
information confidential. We may also release your information when we  
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site  
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be  
provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
 **Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we  
may include or offer third party products or services on our website.  
These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies.  
We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and  
activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the  
integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens  
Online  
Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone  
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all  
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
 **Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected  
through our website and not to information collected offline.  
 **Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the  
use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our  
website at <http://webwash.net/terms-and-conditions>.  
 **Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  
 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those  
changes  
on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  
1/1/2012
